export const questions = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a noun?",
    option1: "Quickly",
    option2: "Run",
    option3: "Happiness",
    option4: "Blue",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which sentence is in the past tense?",
    option1: "She will go to the store",
    option2: "She goes to the store.",
    option3: "She is going to the store.",
    option4: "She went to the store.",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Identify the correct plural form of the word 'mouse'",
    option1: "Mouses",
    option2: "Mices",
    option3: "Mice",
    option4: "Miceses",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Choose the correct form of the verb to complete the sentence: 'She ____ to the gym every day.'",
    option1: "go",
    option2: "going",
    option3: "gone",
    option4: "goes",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which sentence uses the correct comparative adjective?",
    option1: "She is more taller than him.",
    option2: "She is the taller than him.",
    option3: " She is taller than him.",
    option4: " She is tall than him.",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which sentence correctly uses a semicolon?",
    option1: "She loves reading; and he loves writing.",
    option2: "She loves reading; he loves writing.",
    option3: "She loves reading; but he loves writing.",
    option4: "She loves reading; however, he loves writing.",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Identify the sentence with the correct subject-verb agreement.",
    option1: "The dogs runs fast.",
    option2: "The dog run fast.",
    option3: "The dogs run fast.",
    option4: "The dog running fast.",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following sentences is in the passive voice?",
    option1: "The chef cooks the meal.",
    option2: "The meal is cooked by the chef.",
    option3: "The chef is cooking the meal.",
    option4: "The meal cooked by the chef.",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Choose the correct form of the pronoun to complete the sentence: 'Between you and ____, this is a secret.'",
    option1: "me",
    option2: "I",
    option3: "myself",
    option4: "mine",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which sentence correctly uses an apostrophe?",
    option1: "Its a beautiful day.",
    option2: "The dog's tail is wagging.",
    option3: "The dogs tail is wagging.",
    option4: "Its' a beautiful day.",
    ans: 2,
  },
];
